Shafiqul Bari Sadman

Having around 3 years of experience in software industry with track record of working in different project and organization which helped me to adopt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative and able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadline.



- shafiqulbarisadman@gmail.com
- Ohaka, Bangladesh
- S live:.cid.80d829edfde32d8f

- +8801611477929
- in linkedin.com/in/sadman6259
- github.com/sadman6259

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Surbana Jurong Private Limited

01/2022 - Present

Responsibilities

- Requirement analysis, design and develop solution for high volume of data driven IOT based project.
- Work in Every steps of project management from initial layout designing to database design.

Software Engineer

Labaid pharmaceutical Limited

04/2021 - 12/2021

Responsibilities

- Build new modules for ERP System to manage business for a large pharmaceutical company.
- Build a new application from scratch to manage order and sales of a company.

Software Engineer (Part-time) **XTRATECH**

08/2021 - 04/2022

Responsibilites

- Integrate different 3rd party API's (Turkish airlines, Travellanda etc) for travel technology app which is responsible for flight and hotel booking.
- Implement better solution for tuning performance of existing solutions and fix bugs.

Junior Software Engineer PiisTech

11/2019 - 03/2021

Responsibilities

- Build New modules for a CRM as per client requirements and fix existing bugs of the system.
- Directly work with team lead and write efficient code and query to manage business deals

RMR CLOUD (12/2019 - 02/2021)

Accounting and Customer Management Application built in .NET Core Web Api, Angular . It included features like Customer, Lead, Invoice, Inventory, Tickets, Sales, Estimates, Emator, Reports etc.

IEATERY (11/2019 - 03/2020)

 Food ordering and Restaurant Management Software built in. NET MVC, .NET Web Api, Javascript, Jquery. It included features like Order, Menu Management, Restaurants, Sales etc.

EDUCATION

Bsc In CSE

Patuakhali Science And Technology University

01/2016 - 12/2019

CGPA-3.08 (Out of 4.00)

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Sustainable Building Management (01/2022 - Present)

 IOT Project Built in .NET web api and in front end AngularJS to manage building performance like it measures performance of Water, Electricity, Waste, Indoor Air Quality etc.Here I have to deal with large volume of data and various custom charts to visualize data.

Labaid ERP (04/2021 - 12/2021)

 ERP system built in. NET Core Web api and Angular for managing organization business.It covers the whole process in business operation like HRMS,SCM,PPIC,SALES,PMD,Quality Control,INVENTORY etc.

Depot Management System (06/2021 - 12/2021)

.NET Core Web Api and Angular based web application for manage products sales and corresponsing process.It has Features like Invoice, Allocation, Summary, Collection, Stock, Bank deposit

ACHIEVEMENT

Solve 500+ problems in different online judges